Guide to the Creative Time Archive 1973-2006 MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Video and Film, 107335
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Originals, 107338
    - Song Dong, "Evaporating Art", Reuters, 2005; 107372 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0371)
    - "Life During Wartime", 6/12/?, Undated; 107371 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0686)
    - "Living With AIDS: Seize Control of the FDA", Undated; 107370 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0522)
    - # 4, 6/28, Undated; 107369 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0145)
    - [unidentified], Undated; 107368 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0650)
    - [unidentified], Undated; 107367 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0163)
    - [unidentified], Undated; 107366 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0554)
    - 1st Tape "R", Undated; 107365 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0199)
    - Ange Leccia, Undated; 107364 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0359)
    - Art on the Beach (tape 1), Undated; 107363 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0329)
    - Art on the Beach (tape 2, Kay Lynn), Undated; 107362 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0343)
    - Art on the Beach (tape 3, Kay Lynn), Undated; 107361 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0355)
      Format: 3/4"
    - Art on the Beach (tape 5), Undated; 107360 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0375)
    - Bill Shannon, Axis Dance and Solo, Undated; 107359 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0367)
    - Bravo, "Unfinished Stories" (presentation tape), Undated; 107358 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0667)
      Duration: [2 min.]
    - Brooklyn Library, Undated; 107357 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0183)
    - Burlesque Video, 2 Versions, Undated; 107356 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0432)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Pyrotechnic Projects", Undated; 107355 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0664)
    - Dreamland Artist Club, Undated; 107354 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0131)
    - Emergency Broadcast Network, Video Press Kit, Undated; 107353 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0680)
    - Fair and Balanced News/ Freedom, Undated; 107352 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0524)
    - Grand Central Installation, Undated; 107351 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0137)
    - Grand Central Installation, Undated; 107350 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0197)
    - Grand Central Installation, Undated; 107349 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0626)
    - Granular Synthesis, Undated; 107348 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0173)
    - Jim Campbell, "Untitled (Agora)", Undated; 107347 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0205)
    - Joan Giummo, "Fire Sign", Undated; 107346 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0688)
    - Kathy Brew, Roberto Guerra, DNAID, Undated; 107345 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0271)
    - Marjetica Potrc, "Borders" (Tape 1), Undated; 107344 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0179)
    - Marjetica Potrc, "Borders" (tape 2, beginning of general discussion), Undated; 107343 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0628)
    - Susan Cianciolo, "Diadel", Undated; 107342 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0181)
    - Thomas Harris, "AIDs and Art", The Eleventh Hour #266, WNET Thirteen, Undated; 107341 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0685)
    - William Kentridge, Undated; 107340 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0259)
    - Zhang Huan, Undated; 179.0127; 107339 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0127, E-records fales_mss179)
      Original format: MiniDV, Duration: 50 min.
  - Subseries C: Film, 107336
    - Art on the Beach, Undated; 107337 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0698)
      Format: Super 8 film
  - Subseries D: Video Recordings - Submasters - CLOSED
    Conditions Governing Access
    CLOSED
    - ID: 179.0686 - 179.0773, undated (Box PM 8)
      Scope and Contents
      Contains materials numbered 179.0686, 179.0689, 179.0692, 179.0695, 179.0698, 179.0701, 179.0704, 179.0707, 179.0710, 179.0713, 179.0716, 179.0719, 179.0722, 179.0725, 179.0728, 179.0731, 179.0734, 179.0737, 179.0740, 179.0743, 179.0746, 179.0749, 179.0752, 179.0755, 179.0758, 179.0761, 179.0764, 179.0767, 179.0770, 179.0773
    - Masstransiscope by Bill Brand 1980, 2008 (Box PM 10, Case 179.0775)
  - Subseries E: Video Recordings - Preservation Masters - CLOSED
    - ID: 179.0685 - 179.0724 (Box PM 49)
    - ID: 179.0727 - 179.0766 (Box PM 50)
    - ID: 179.0679, 179.0772 (Box PM 51)
- Series VI: Audio, 107209
  This series includes audio recordings from the Creative Time Archive. Titles are arranged chronologically by year. Compilation tapes are arranged chronologically by first year represented on tape. Material includes performances, news broadcasts, speeches, source material, and other miscellaneous recordings. Researcher access is limited to Subseries A – Audio Recordings – Access Copies.
  - Subseries A: Audio Recordings - Access Copies, 107269
    - Art on the Beach, 1985; 107334 (Case 179.0075)
      Format: CD-R
      Original Original Format: Audio cassette
    - Art on the Beach - NPR, 9/3/85 [Press], 1985; 107333 (Case 179.0108)
      Original Format: Audio cassette
    - Art on the Beach - side a: Last Day Concert; side b: 9/14/85 [part 1], 1985; 107332 (Case 179.0120)
    - Art on the Beach - side a: Last Day Concert; side b: 9/14/85 [part 2], 1985; 107331 (Case 179.0121)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Guerrilla Girls, 6/16/87, 1987; 107330 (Case 179.0086)
    - Lenny Pickett with the Borneo Horns, [1987]; 107329 (Case 179.0044)
    - Live Recordings from [1987-]1988 (for NEA Music Program FY90), 107328 (Case 179.0088)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Joan Jonas Soundtrack, [1988]; 107327 (Case 179.0079)
    - Recordings from 1988-1991 (for NEA Music Program FY92), 107326 (Case 179.0116)
    - "Video/Musica", Nov 1989 [part 1], 107325 (Case 179.0063)
    - "Video/Musica", Nov 1989 [part 2], 107324 (Case 179.0064)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Christiane Vaillancourt, NPR, July 1989 [Press], 107323 (Case 179.0040)
    - Art in the Anchorage - NPR Broadcast, 7/27/89 [Press], 1989; 107322 (Case 179.0048)
    - Bob Holman Interview, "Poets in the Bars", NOMMO Radio, 4/11/89, 1989; 107321 (Case 179.0094)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Arthur Russell, 9/6/91, 1991; 107320 (Case 179.0028)
      Original Format: DAT cassette
    - Art in the Anchorage - Bosho, 9/7/91, 1991; 107319 (Case 179.0026)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Guy Yarden, 9/7/91, 1991; 107318 (Case 179.0030)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Hugo Largo, 9/5/91, 1991; 107317 (Case 179.0032)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Linda Fisher, 9/05/91, 1991; 107316 (Case 179.0024)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Linda Fisher, 9/5/91, 1991; 107315 (Case 179.0110)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Manhattan Marimba Quartet, 1991; 107314 (Case 179.0058)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Manhattan Marimba Quartet, 9/6/91, 1991; 107313 (Case 179.0056)
    - Jerri Allyn, "Angels Have Been Sent To Me" [side a: Eng; side b: Spa] [part 1], 1991; 107312 (Case 179.0103)
    - Jerri Allyn, "Angels Have Been Sent To Me" [side a: Eng; side b: Spa] [part 2], 1991; 107311 (Case 179.0104)
    - Music Samples, Spring 1991 [part 1], 107310 (Case 179.0068)
    - Music Samples, Spring 1991 [part 2], 107309 (Case 179.0069)
    - Selections for NEA Review, 1991; 107308 (Case 179.0052)
    - John Pietro, compilation tape, 1992; 107307 (Case 179.0042)
    - Masterpieces Without The Director, Milk Carton Project, WBAI, 2/8/92 [Press], 1992; 107306 (Case 179.0054)
      Duration: [59 min.]
    - Norman Salant, "Saxophone Stories", 10/92, 1992; 107305 (Case 179.0066)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - NPR, 7/8/93 [Press], 1993; 107304 (Case 179.0106)
    - Board Meeting, 9/29/93 [part 1], 1993; 107303 (Case 179.0083)
    - Board Meeting, 9/29/93 [part 2], 1993; 107302 (Case 179.0084)
    - Norman Salant, "sax/on", "After Ours" [part 1], 1994; 107301 (Case 179.0060)
    - Norman Salant, "sax/on", "After ours" [part 2], 1994; 107300 (Case 179.0061)
    - Julia Meltzer, Amanda Ramos, "Chatlandia, 3 Conversations", [1995]; 107299 (Case 179.0118)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Ben Neill, July 27 [part 1], [1996]; 107298 (Case 179.0034)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Ben Neill, July 27 [part 2], [1996]; 107297 (Case 179.0035)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Vernon Reid, July 27 [part 1], [1996]; 107296 (Case 179.0037)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Vernon Reid, July 27 [part 2], [1996]; 107295 (Case 179.0038)
    - Paco Cao, [1996]; 107294 (Case 179.0010)
      Original Format: Microcassette
    - Phil Kline, "Winter Music", 12/96, 1996; 107293 (Case 179.0073)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Adrianne Wortzel proposal, 2/25/97, 1997; 107292 (Case 179.0071)
    - Guillermo Gomez-Pena, "El Mexterminator", 1997, 107291 (Case 179.0112)
    - "El Mexterminator", WBAI Voices Against the Wall, 6/5/98 [Press] [part 1], 1998; 107290 (Case 179.0100)
    - "El Mexterminator", WBAI Voices Against the Wall, 6/5/98 [Press] [part 2], 1998; 107289 (Case 179.0101)
    - Karen Finley, "A Message from…", 1-900-ALL-KAREN, 2/16/98, 1998; 107288 (Case 179.0090)
    - Shimon Attie, "Tribute to Joe Papp", 11/1/98, 1998; 107287 (Case 179.0081)
    - CT Interview - Anne Pasternak, 10/09/01, "On WTC response", 2001; 107286 (Case 179.0018)
    - CT Interview - Anne Pasternak, 12/03/01, "General", 2001; 107285 (Case 179.0020)
    - CT Interview - Carol Stakenas, 10/26/01, 2001; 107284 (Case 179.0012)
      Duration: [55 min.]
    - CT Interview - Elizabeth Iarrappino, 11/9/01, 2001; 107283 (Case 179.0002)
    - CT Interview - Kelly Evans, 11/14/01, 2001; 107282 (Case 179.0008)
    - CT Interview - Kevin [McHugh], 11/09/01, 2001; 107281 (Case 179.0022)
    - CT Interview - Prof. Harriet Senie, 11/29/01, 2001; 107280 (Case 179.0006)
    - CT Interview - Rachel Stevens, 11/12/01, 2001; 107279 (Case 179.0014)
    - CT Interview - Sarah Bacon, 11/02/01, 2001; 107278 (Case 179.0016)
      Duration: [40 min.]
    - Memorial Discussion, 3/28/02 (1 of 2), 2002; 107277 (Case 179.0097)
    - Memorial Meeting, NYU, 3/28/02 (1 of 2), 2002; 107276 (Case 179.0098)
    - Anita Contini Interview, Artists' Space, Christian Science Monitor (Cut #4), Undated; 107275 (Case 179.0092)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Closing Party, Tape #1, Undated; 107274 (Case 179.0077)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Closing Party, Tape #2, Undated; 107273 (Case 179.0050)
    - Calvin Trillin, Undated; 107272 (Case 179.0114)
    - Karen Tape, Undated; 107271 (Case 179.0004)
    - NEA Music Tape Copy, Undated; 107270 (Case 179.0046)
  - Subseries B: Audio Recordings - Originals, 107210
    - Ann Wilson, "Butler's Lives of the Saints", Jan 1978, 107268 (Box 32, Reel 179.0699, E-records fales_mss179, E-records 179.0699)
      1/4" Open Reel Audio, 87 min.
      Preservation note: "3.75 ips, half-track stereo, uni-directional, files split in two to conform to JHOVE validation standards"
    - Art on the Beach, 1985; 107267 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0074)
      Format: Audio cassette
    - Art on the Beach - NPR, 9/3/85 [Press], 1985; 107266 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0107)
    - Art on the Beach - side a: Last Day Concert; side b: 9/14/85, 1985; 107265 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0119)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Guerrilla Girls, 6/16/87, 1987; 107264 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0085)
    - Lenny Pickett with the Borneo Horns, [1987]; 107263 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0043)
    - Live Recordings from [1987-]1988 (for NEA Music Program FY90), 107262 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0087)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Joan Jonas Soundtrack, [1988]; 107261 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0078)
    - Recordings from 1988-1991 (for NEA Music Program FY92), 107260 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0115)
    - "Video/Musica", Nov 1989, 107259 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0062)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Christiane Vaillancourt, NPR, July 1989 [Press], 107258 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0039)
    - Art in the Anchorage - NPR Broadcast, 7/27/89 [Press], 1989; 107257 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0047)
    - Bob Holman Interview, "Poets in the Bars", NOMMO Radio, 4/11/89, 1989; 107256 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0093)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Arthur Russell, 9/6/91, 1991; 107255 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0027)
      Format: DAT cassette
    - Art in the Anchorage - Bosho, 9/7/91, 1991; 107254 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0025)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Guy Yarden, 9/7/91, 1991; 107253 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0029)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Hugo Largo, 9/5/91, 1991; 107252 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0031)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Linda Fisher, 9/05/91, 1991; 107251 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0023)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Linda Fisher, 9/5/91, 1991; 107250 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0109)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Manhattan Marimba Quartet, 1991; 107249 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0057)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Manhattan Marimba Quartet, 9/6/91, 1991; 107248 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0055)
    - Jerri Allyn, "Angels Have Been Sent To Me" [side a: Eng; side b: Spa], 1991; 107247 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0102)
    - Music Samples, Spring 1991, 107246 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0067)
    - Selections for NEA Review, 1991; 107245 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0051)
    - John Pietro, compilation tape, 1992; 107244 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0041)
    - Masterpieces Without The Director, Milk Carton Project, WBAI, 2/8/92 [Press], 1992; 107243 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0053)
    - Norman Salant, "Saxophone Stories", 10/92, 1992; 107242 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0065)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - NPR, 7/8/93 [Press], 1993; 107241 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0105)
    - Board Meeting, 9/29/93, 1993; 107240 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0082)
    - Norman Salant, "sax/on", "After Ours", 1994; 107239 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0059)
    - Julia Meltzer, Amanda Ramos, "Chatlandia, 3 Conversations", [1995]; 107238 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0117)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Ben Neill, July 27, [1996]; 107237 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0033)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Vernon Reid, July 27, [1996]; 107236 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0036)
    - Paco Cao, [1996]; 107235 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0009)
      Format: Microcassette
    - Phil Kline, "Winter Music", 12/96, 1996; 107234 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0072)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Adrianne Wortzel proposal, 2/25/97, 1997; 107233 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0070)
    - Guillermo Gomez-Pena, "El Mexterminator", 1997, 107232 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0111)
    - "El Mexterminator", WBAI Voices Against the Wall, 6/5/98 [Press], 1998; 107231 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0099)
    - Karen Finley, "A Message from…", 1-900-ALL-KAREN, 2/16/98, 1998; 107230 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0089)
    - Karen Finley, "A Message from…", 1-900-ALL-KAREN, 2/16/98, 1998; 107229 (Box not specified, Folder ID: 179.0122)
    - Shimon Attie, "Tribute to Joe Papp", 11/1/98, 1998; 107228 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0080)
    - CT Interview - Anne Pasternak, 10/09/01, "On WTC response", 2001; 107227 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0017)
    - CT Interview - Anne Pasternak, 12/03/01, "General", 2001; 107226 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0019)
    - CT Interview - Carol Stakenas, 10/26/01, 2001; 107225 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0011)
    - CT Interview - Elizabeth Iarrappino, 11/9/01, 2001; 107224 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0001)
    - CT Interview - Kelly Evans, 11/14/01, 2001; 107223 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0007)
    - CT Interview - Kevin [McHugh], 11/09/01, 2001; 107222 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0021)
    - CT Interview - Prof. Harriet Senie, 11/29/01, 2001; 107221 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0005)
    - CT Interview - Rachel Stevens, 11/12/01, 2001; 107220 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0013)
    - CT Interview - Sarah Bacon, 11/02/01, 2001; 107219 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0015)
    - Memorial Discussion, 3/28/02 (1 of 2), 2002; 107218 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0095)
    - Memorial Meeting, NYU, 3/28/02 (1 of 2), 2002; 107217 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0096)
    - Anita Contini Interview, Artists' Space, Christian Science Monitor (Cut #4), Undated; 107216 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0091)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Closing Party, Tape #1, Undated; 107215 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0076)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Closing Party, Tape #2, Undated; 107214 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0049)
    - Calvin Trillin, Undated; 107213 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0113)
    - Karen Tape, Undated; 107212 (Box not specified, Folder ID: 179.0003)
    - NEA Music Tape Copy, Undated; 107211 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0045)
- Series VII: Mail Art - Marcos Kurtycz, 107119
  This series consists of various mailed objects created by artist Marcos Kurtycz including postcards, correspondence, books, performance and exhibition flyers, posters, and many art objects sent between 1988 and 1990 to Debbie Levine and Cee Scott Brown of Creative Time. Additional mailed objects from Kurtycz may be found in Oversize Series.
  - Misc. Kurtycz Exhibition/Performance cards, 1979,1989,1989; 107208 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Clipping - "Accion al Mediodia" performance photo montage, Chapultepec, Mexico, 1984; 107207 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - "Mira" book by Marcos Kurtycz and Anna Kutycz, 15 May 1987, 107206 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Envelopes, addressed to Cee Brown and Debbie Levine, Creative Time [5 items], 1988-1989; 107205 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - "Fuegomar" performance documentation booklet by Kurtycz, February 1988, 107204 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - "Taller de Juguete Magico" art proposal book by Kurtycz, 16 March 1988, 107203 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - "Zero Village" stamped sheets with envelope, 30 June 1988, 107202 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - "Zero Village" performance flyers, Yellow Springs Institute, 16 July 1988, 107201 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Yellow Springs Institute program information, Kurtycz residency acceptance letter, 1988; 107200 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - August 1988, 107199 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - "Do You Know Hockers?" book by Kurtycz, for Kurtix' Softwars Matrix, August 1988 [2 copies], 107198 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - "Hocker" printed tablecloth - "The Morning After Therapy", 11 December 1988, 107086 (Box 23)
  - "Hocker" sheets, for Kurtix' Softwars Matrix, August 1988 [8 unique sheets], 107197 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - September 1988, 107196 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Envelopes - October 1988 [7 items], 107195 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - October 1988, 107194 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 7 October 1988, 107193 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 13 October 1988, 107192 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 13 October 1988, 107191 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 13 October 1988 [not postmarked], 107190 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Lead [metal] "Hocker" artwork with note, 20 October 1988, 107189 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 24 October 1988, 107188 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 24 October 1988, 107187 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - "Organikwars" flyers [for Creative Time performance] with letter, 26 October 1988, 107186 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Envelopes - November 1988 [10 items], 107185 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Postcard(s) - "Softwars Cardpost", 3 November 1988, 107184 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 5 November 1988, 107183 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Misc. flyers - "Up Tiempo", "Softwars", "Preempting Swarm", etc., stamped 5 November 1988, 107182 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 7 November 1988, 107181 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 7 November 1988 [not postmarked], 107180 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 9 November 1988, 107179 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 9 November 1988, 107178 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Postcard - 14 November 1988, 107177 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 21 November 1988, 107176 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 22 November 1988, 107175 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Postcard - 24 November 1988, 107174 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - "Tercera Gracia de Via Angelina" prints, 24 November 1988, 107173 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 28 November 1988, 107172 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", November 1988, 107171 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - "Artforum Bombing Action" performance booklet (San Diego, CA, 1985), mailed November 1988, 107170 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Misc. Mail Art - November 1988 [4 items], 107169 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Mail Art - "Organikwars Triptych", December 1988 [not postmarked], 107168 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - "Heart of Calm" (poem by Kim Niemala Duggan) assorted flyers for "Organikwars Triptych", December 1988, 107167 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - "Border+ing Manual" book by Kurtycz, "Softwars Editions", 1988; 107166 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Envelope - February 1989, 107165 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence - February 1989, 107164 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - "Island Discovery" book by Kurtycz for "NYPR89EKT", with letter to Martha Wilson, 14 February 1989, 107163 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Postcard - 7 March 1989, 107162 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence - "Biheaded Island", 17 March 1989, 107161 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence - 19 March 1989, 107160 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Postcard - "NYPR89EKT", March 1989, 107159 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence - 4 April 1989, 107158 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 24 June 1989, 107157 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Envelope - 8 July 1989, 107156 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - "Butterfny" prototypes, "NYPR89EKT" [2 unique items], 1989; 107155 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - "Reverse Degrading" artwork, "NYPR89EKT", 1989; 107154 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - "Reverse Degrading" artwork, "NYPR89EKT", Creekwood Editions, January 1989, 107153 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Misc. "NYPR89EKT" artwork [7 items], 1989; 107152 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - "Rumi's Room" booklet by Kurtycz, edited for Softwars Matrix, 1989; 107151 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Envelope - December 1990, 107150 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Misc. "XYZOMPANTLI" performance materials, with note to Cee Brown, 17 December 1990, 107149 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Misc. Mail Art - "Organikwars" [not postmarked], Undated; 107148 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Misc. Mail Art - "Organikwars" [not postmarked] [3 items], Undated; 107147 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost" [not postmarked], Undated; 107146 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Postcard - "Software Cardpost" [not postmarked], Undated; 107145 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - "El Labertinto de Kurtycz" book by Kurtycz [2 items], Undated; 107144 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - "Maiz" book by Kurtycz, Guaytalpa Editions, Undated; 107143 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - "Mi Casa" book by Kurtycz, Softwars MacroMex Editions [3 items], Undated; 107142 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Lead [metal] "Hocker" artwork with note, Undated; 107141 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - "Agrest" artwork, Undated; 107140 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Misc. untitled artworks [5 items], Undated; 107139 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - "Laurie Anderson for Softwars Organikwars" sheets, Undated; 107138 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Misc. untitled faces print, Undated; 107137 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - "Organikwars Hockers" stamped images [7 unique sheets], Undated; 107136 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - "Organikwars Topsy-Turvy Hocker" artwork, Undated; 107135 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - "The Wheel" artworks, "Organikwars" [2 unique items], Undated; 107134 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - "Organikwars" faces folded print, Undated; 107133 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - "Organikwars Hocker" card, Undated; 107132 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - "Organikwars Editor Hocker" artwork, Undated; 107131 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - "Organikwars Editor" artwork, Undated; 107130 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Postcard - "C'Mamoth", "Softwars Cardpost" [not postmarked], Undated; 107129 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - "Organikwars: Limited Up Tiempo" folded print, Undated; 107128 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - "Grinding of Hockers" stamped page, Undated; 107127 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - "Oftenly, it's painful to be a Hocker" print, Undated; 107126 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - "Glorious 88", Softwars MacroMex Editions, Undated; 107125 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Photograph - Kurtycz working on roof, Undated; 107124 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Sticker sheets - "Hocker"; "NYPR89EKT", Undated; 107123 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Paper Bag - "Organikwars Hocker", Undated; 107122 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Envelopes - "Taller Visual" [not postmarked], Undated; 107121 (Box 20, Folder 88)